A Guide to the Overseas Development Council records FA788
Rockefeller Archive Center
Overseas Development Council records
1967-2000
Rockefeller Archive Center
Overseas Development Council
FA788
25.79 Cubic Feet 67 letter document boxes, 1 half-letter document box, and 1 photo box
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement note
The Overseas Development Council Records are organized into 14 series:
Series 1: Vital Records Series 2: Board and Council Records Series 3: Meetings Series 4: Fundraising Series 5: Country Files Series 6: Kudos, Testimony, and Speeches Series 7: Press Clippings Series 8: Proposals and Projects Series 9: Corporations Series 10: Foundations Series 11: International Organizations Series 12: Publications Series 13: Financial Records Series 14: Photographs
Scope and Contents Note
The Overseas Development Council (ODC), disbanded in 2000, was a policy research institution.
These records contain the main organizational records, including financial records, meeting minutes, reports on development proposals, and photographs.
- Vital Records, 1967-2000; 1; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
  - ODC Closing - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Policy Manual, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bylaws/Articles of Incorporation, 1969-1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors, Council Inclusion Policy (Bd. Mtgs), 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Conflict of Interest Policy, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Council Membership Responsibilities, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors, Membership Responsibilities, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Board By-Laws, 1995 December 15 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors Membership History, 1969-2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - BCL Resignations & Retirements, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - BCL Resignations & Retirements, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Nominating Committee, Council Expansion History, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Fourth Annual Convocation, 1993 October 13-14 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Third Annual Convocation, 1991 June 24-25 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - First Annual Convocation, 1988 December 7 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Compliance and Evaluation - Year 2000, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Annual Reports, 1971-1998 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Pamphlets, 1982-1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - History - 25th Anniversary, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - History - Transition, 1968-1983 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - ODC Historical Background Info., 1969-1995 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Articles on Formation of ODC, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Murden Report (Prelude to Creation of ODC), 1967 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - President's Reports, 1978-1985 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - President's Reports, 1985-1989 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Activities Reports, 1981-1985 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Activities Reports, 1985-1994 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Activities Reports, 1994-1997 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Activities Reports, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - President's Reports, 1990, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Board and Council Records, 1969-2000; 2; 8.36 Cubic Feet 22 letter document boxes
  - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Nominating Committee Meeting Minutes, 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1991-1995 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1985-1990 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Board of Directors Resolutions, 1987-1993 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Board of Directors & Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Board of Directors Bios, 1993-1997 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Board of Directors Membership Lists, 1969-1992 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Chairman Search - Barnevik, Percy Nils, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    Conditions Governing Access note
    Restricted from access - Open in 2026
  - Chairman Search - Cardenas, Dr. Mauricio, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Chairman Search - Buvinic, Mayra, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Chairman Search - Brundtland, Gro Harlem, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Chairman Search - Carlsson, Ingvar, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Chairman Search - Chase, Warren S., 1995 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Chairman Search - Deere, Dr. Carmen, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Chairman Search - Dyson, Ester, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Chairman Search - Evans, Gareth, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Chairman Search - Gyllenhammer, Pehr, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Chairman Search - Kakabadse, Yolanda, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Chairman Search - Knowles, Marie L., 1995 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Chairman Search - Laudato, George, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Chairman Search - Lawson, Nigel, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Chairman Search - Lubbers, The Honorable Rudolphus, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Chairman Search - Norberg, Carl, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Chairman Search - Raczynski, Dr. Dagmar, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Chairman Search - Ramphele, Mamphela, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Chairman Search - Han, Seung-Soo, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Chairman Search - Stallings, Barbara, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Chairman Search - Stavenhagen, Dr. Rodolfo, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Chairman Search - Volcker, Paul, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Chairman Search - Wallenberg, Marcus, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Chairman Search - Wilson, Stephanie, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Chairman Search - Yudelman, Sally, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Board and Council Members, 1986-2000; 1
    - Aaron, David L., 1993 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Ahmad, Datuk Khatijah, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Albright, Madeline - C94, 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Anderson, Lisa - C94, 1991-1995 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Anderson, Robert O. - C94, 1969-1998 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Asencio, Diego C. - C94, 1988-1998 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Asher, Robert E., 1977-2000 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Aspe-Armella, Pedro - '96, 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Assevero, Vicki Ann, 1990-1998 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Atwood, J. Brian, 1989-1993 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Baeza, Mario - 1996, 1994-1998 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Baker, Gwendolyn Calvert - 1996, 1993-1998 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Barnes, Michael D., 1987-2000 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Barry, Nancy - 1996, 1993-1998 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Bartell, Ernest, 1988-1998 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Barth, Norman, 1988-1998 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Bausch, James J., 1988-1998 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Bell, Peter D., 1987-1998 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Bennet, Douglas J., 1981-1993 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Benton, Marjorie C., 1987-1998 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Benton, Phillip E., Jr., 1993-1998 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Birdsall, Nancy, 1993-2000 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Berger, Louis, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Beyer, John C. - 1995, 1992-1998 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Bobadilla, Dr. Jose-Luis, 1993-1995 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Bogdanowicz-Bindert, Christine A., 1994-1998 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Bolin, William H., 1983-1999 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Botchwey, Kwesi, 1995-1998 (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - Bowie, Robert R., 1971-1995 (Box 6, Folder 93)
    - Brademas, John, 1987-2000 (Box 6, Folder 94)
    - Brainard, Lawrence J., 1990-1994 (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - Biester, Edward G., Jr., 1994-1998 (Box 6, Folder 96)
    - Breen, J. Richard, 1987-1998 (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - Brown, Keith L. - C95, 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 98)
    - Brown, Lester R., 1995-1998 (Box 6, Folder 99)
    - Bruce, Judith, 1993-1998 (Box 6, Folder 100)
    - Burnham, James B., 1990-1999 (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Byron, Reverend William J., S.J., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - Camp, Sharon L., 1988-1998 (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - Campbell, Colin G., 1988-1998 (Box 7, Folder 104)
    - Campbell, Willie, 1988-2000 (Box 7, Folder 105)
    - Catley-Carlson, Margaret, 1992-1999 (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - Challenor, Herschelle S., 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - Chayes, Antonia H., 1989-1996 (Box 7, Folder 108)
    - Chen, Lincoln, 1990-1998 (Box 7, Folder 109)
    - Clark, Noreen - 1996, 1993-1997 (Box 7, Folder 110)
    - Clark, Richard C., 1991-1995 (Box 7, Folder 111)
    - Clausen, A. W., 1980-1998 (Box 7, Folder 112)
    - Chamberlain, Mariam, 1994-1998 (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - Cooper, Kerry - 1996, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 114)
    - Constable, Pamela - 1996, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - Coopersmith, Esther L., 1988-1999 (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - Cox, Robert, 1993-1998 (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - Cutter, Curtis C., 1994-1998 (Box 7, Folder 118)
    - Dale, Francis L., 1986-1994 (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - Dammeyer, Rod, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 120)
    - Davis, Susan - 1996, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 121)
    - Dawson, Marion - 1996, 1995-1999 (Box 7, Folder 122)
    - Debs, Richard, 1987-2000 (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - Dentzer, William T., Jr., 1994-2000 (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - Derryck, Vivian L., 1989-1999 (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - Derham, Richard, 1994-1998 (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - Draper, William, III, 1991-1998 (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - Drayton, William - 1996, 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 128)
    - Duff, Patricia - 1996, 1994-1999 (Box 8, Folder 129)
    - Dulany, Peggy - 1994-1995, 1993-2000 (Box 8, Folder 130)
    - Dulany, Peggy, 1984-1993 (Box 8, Folder 131)
    - Dunlop, Joan B., 1989-1999 (Box 8, Folder 132)
    - Eberle, William D., 1985-1996 (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - Ehrlich, Thomas, 1986-1995 (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - Eizenstat, Stuart, 1991-1999 (Box 8, Folder 135)
    - Erb, Guy F., 1978-1996 (Box 8, Folder 136)
    - Farmer, Thomas L., Esq., 1969-1995 (Box 8, Folder 137)
    - Fierce, Hughlyn F., 1990-1995 (Box 8, Folder 138)
    - Fisher, Robert, 1977-1998 (Box 8, Folder 139)
    - FitzGerald, Frances, 1992-1998 (Box 9, Folder 140)
    - Foxley, Hon. Alejandro, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 141)
    - Fredericks, J. Wayne, 1974-1987 (Box 8, Folder 142)
    - Fredericks, J. Wayne, 1988-1999 (Box 9, Folder 143)
    - Freeman, Harry - 1994-1995, 1994-1997 (Box 9, Folder 144)
      Restricted from access - Personnel
    - Freeman, Harry L., 1986-1996 (Box 9, Folder 145)
    - Freeman, Orville L., 1979-1999 (Box 9, Folder 146)
    - Friedman, Stephen J., 1982-1992 (Box 9, Folder 147)
    - Friedman, Stephen J., 1987-2000 (Box 9, Folder 148)
    - Friedman, Stephen J. - 1994-1995, 1994-2000 (Box 10, Folder 149)
    - Fuller, Kathryn S., 1991-1998 (Box 10, Folder 150)
    - Fuller, William P., 1994-1997 (Box 10, Folder 151)
    - de la Garza, Rodolfo O., 1994-1999 (Box 10, Folder 152)
    - Gilligan, John J., 1981-1998 (Box 10, Folder 153)
    - Goldman, Charles N., 1988-1995 (Box 10, Folder 154)
    - Gordon, Lincoln, 1969-1995 (Box 10, Folder 155)
    - Grindle, Merilee S. - 1996, 1994-2000 (Box 10, Folder 156)
    - Growald, Paul J., 1993-1998 (Box 10, Folder 157)
    - Gunther, Herbert Chao - 1996, 1993-1998 (Box 10, Folder 158)
    - Gyohten, Toyoo, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 159)
    - Hall, Janet, 1988-1997 (Box 10, Folder 160)
    - Hamilton, Edward K., 1969-1978 (Box 10, Folder 161)
    - Hamilton, Edward K., 1979-1995 (Box 11, Folder 162)
    - Hamilton, Edward K., 1986-2000 (Box 11, Folder 163)
    - Hamilton, Edward K. - Democratic Study Group, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 164)
    - Hamilton, Edward K. - Research Papers, 1969-1977 (Box 11, Folder 165)
    - Hart, Peter D., 1988-1994 (Box 11, Folder 166)
    - Hauser, Rita E., 1988-1998 (Box 11, Folder 167)
    - Hayden, Rose L., 1985-1995 (Box 11, Folder 168)
    - Hehir, Rev. J. Bryan, 1992-1999 (Box 11, Folder 169)
    - Herzstein, Robert E., Esq., 1988-2000 (Box 11, Folder 170)
    - Heldring, Frederick, 1982-1997 (Box 11, Folder 171)
    - Hesburgh, Theodore, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 172)
    - Hesburgh, Theodore, 1982-1987 (Box 12, Folder 173)
    - Hesburgh, Theodore, 1988-2000 (Box 12, Folder 174)
    - Hinerfeld, Ruth, 1977-2000 (Box 12, Folder 175)
    - Hoagland, Donald W., 1987-1998 (Box 12, Folder 176)
    - Holmes, Joan, 1983-1997 (Box 12, Folder 177)
    - Hormats, Robert D., 1978-1996 (Box 12, Folder 178)
    - Hoskins, Shirley A. - 1996, 1993-1995 (Box 13, Folder 179)
    - Huston, Perdita - 1996, 1993-1995 (Box 13, Folder 180)
    - Jackson, Lois M., 1990-1995 (Box 13, Folder 181)
    - Jacobson, Jerome, 1984-2000 (Box 13, Folder 182)
    - Jaquette, Jane, 1991-1995 (Box 13, Folder 183)
    - Jennings, Peter, 1987-1996 (Box 13, Folder 184)
    - Johnson, Raymond F., 1990-2000 (Box 13, Folder 185)
    - Johnson, Roland H., 1988-1995 (Box 13, Folder 186)
    - Johnson, Willard, 1988-1997 (Box 13, Folder 187)
    - Jordan, Vernon E., Esq., 1969-1995 (Box 13, Folder 188)
    - Joseph, James A., 1990-1995 (Box 13, Folder 189)
    - Kamm, Linda Heller, 1996-1998 (Box 13, Folder 190)
    - Kaplan, Helene, 1989-1998 (Box 13, Folder 191)
    - Keller, Edmond J., Ph.D. - 1995, 1992-1996 (Box 13, Folder 192)
    - King, Colbert I., 1988-1994 (Box 13, Folder 193)
    - Kipper, Judith, 1991-1996 (Box 13, Folder 194)
    - Klutznick, Philip M., 1980-1992 (Box 13, Folder 195)
    - Knapp, J. Burke, 1982-2000 (Box 13, Folder 196)
    - Krogh, Peter F., 1970-1995 (Box 13, Folder 197)
    - Kuczynski, Pedro-Pablo, 1983-1995 (Box 14, Folder 198)
    - Kunstadter, Geraldine S., 1982-2000 (Box 14, Folder 199)
    - Lake, Anthony, 1973-2000 (Box 14, Folder 200)
    - Lamy, Pascal, 1995-2000 (Box 14, Folder 201)
    - Lankester, Sir Timothy, 1989-2000 (Box 14, Folder 202)
    - Leet, Mildred Robbins, 1988-2000 (Box 14, Folder 203)
    - Lill, Edward J., 1994-1998 (Box 14, Folder 204)
    - LLewellyn, J. Bruce, 1988-1994 (Box 14, Folder 205)
    - Lord, Bette Bao, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 206)
    - Lowenthal, Abraham F., 1986-1999 (Box 14, Folder 207)
    - Loy, Frank E., 1986-1998 (Box 14, Folder 208)
    - Lucas, C. Payne, 1974-1993 (Box 14, Folder 209)
    - Lucas, C. Payne, 1994-2000 (Box 15, Folder 210)
    - MacCormack, Charles F. - 1996, 1993-1995 (Box 15, Folder 211)
    - Mahoney, Margaret E., 1988-1998 (Box 15, Folder 212)
    - Martin, Edwin M., 1977-1995 (Box 15, Folder 213)
    - Mathews, Jessica Tuchman, 1988-1994 (Box 15, Folder 214)
    - Maynes, Charles William, 1987-1997 (Box 15, Folder 215)
    - McCabe, Jewell Jackson, 1989-1995 (Box 15, Folder 216)
    - McLean, Sheila Avrin, 1988-1998 (Box 15, Folder 217)
    - McCleary, Paul F., 1982-1998 (Box 15, Folder 218)
    - McCleary, Paul - 1990-1995, 1990-1998 (Box 15, Folder 219)
    - McDougall, Gay J., 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 220)
    - McHenry, Donald F., 1989-1999 (Box 15, Folder 221)
    - McKee, Katherine W., 1988-1995 (Box 15, Folder 222)
    - McNamara, Robert S., 1974-1981 (Box 16, Folder 223)
    - McNamara, Robert S., 1982 (Box 16, Folder 224)
    - McNamara, Robert S., 1983-1989 (Box 16, Folder 225)
    - McNamara, Robert S., 1990-2000 (Box 16, Folder 226)
    - McPherson, M. Peter, 1989-1999 (Box 17, Folder 227)
    - McQuade, Lawrence C., 1985-2000 (Box 17, Folder 228)
    - Mellor, John W., 1977-1998 (Box 17, Folder 229)
    - Moss, Ambler, Ph.D. - 1995, 1992-1995 (Box 17, Folder 230)
    - Moten, Sarah E. - 1996, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 231)
    - Murphy, Ernest L. - 1996, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 232)
    - Mule, Harris M., 1995-1999 (Box 17, Folder 233)
    - Murphy, Paul T., 1992-2000 (Box 17, Folder 234)
    - Murray, Douglas P., 1988-1998 (Box 17, Folder 235)
    - Musser, Marcie J., 1988-1998 (Box 17, Folder 236)
    - Nathan, Robert R., 1983-1994 (Box 17, Folder 237)
    - Nelson, Charles J., 1992-2000 (Box 17, Folder 238)
    - Nelson, Merlin E., 1984-2000 (Box 17, Folder 239)
    - Nevas, Leo, 1988-1993 (Box 17, Folder 240)
    - Nugent, Randolph, 1972-1990 (Box 17, Folder 241)
    - Nye, Joseph S., 1979-1993 (Box 17, Folder 242)
    - O'Reilly, Anthony J.F., 1990-1999 (Box 17, Folder 243)
    - Palmieri, Victor H., 1985 (Box 18, Folder 244)
    - Palmieri, Victor H., 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 245)
    - Palmieri, Victor H., 1992-1999 (Box 18, Folder 246)
    - Palmieri, Victor H. - Papers and Documents, 1983-1993 (Box 18, Folder 247)
    - Pangestu, Dr. Mari, 1997-1999 (Box 18, Folder 248)
    - Pennington, Hilary C., 1989-1995 (Box 18, Folder 249)
    - Perkins, James A., 1969-1998 (Box 18, Folder 250)
    - Perkins, John M. - 1996, 1993-1995 (Box 18, Folder 251)
    - Perlman, Janice - 1996, 1993-1995 (Box 18, Folder 252)
    - Perlmutter, Louis, 1988-1999 (Box 19, Folder 253)
    - Pfeiffer, Jane C., 1979-1999 (Box 19, Folder 254)
    - Pharr, Susan J., 1990-1994 (Box 19, Folder 255)
    - Phillips, Ann, 1988-1998 (Box 19, Folder 256)
    - Pinstrup-Andersen, Per - 1996, 1993-1997 (Box 19, Folder 257)
    - Pressberg, Gail - 1996, 1993-2000 (Box 19, Folder 258)
    - Purcell, Susan Kaufman, 1987-1998 (Box 19, Folder 259)
    - Rabinowitch, Victor, 1997-2000 (Box 19, Folder 260)
    - Raven, Peter H., 1987-1998 (Box 19, Folder 261)
    - Richardson, Henry J., III, 1988-1995 (Box 19, Folder 262)
    - Reynolds, John - Legal Counsel, 1993-2000 (Box 19, Folder 263)
    - Richardson, Elliot L., 1987-1998 (Box 19, Folder 264)
    - Robinson, Pearl, Ph.D., 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 265)
    - Rogers, William D., Esq., 1977-1998 (Box 19, Folder 266)
    - Rotberg, Eugene H., 1988-1998 (Box 19, Folder 267)
    - Rubin, Nancy H., 1985-1997 (Box 19, Folder 268)
    - Sacks, Paul M., 1989-1997 (Box 19, Folder 269)
    - Schaetzel, J. Robert, 1983-1991 (Box 20, Folder 270)
    - Schmidheiny, Stephan, 1992-1994 (Box 20, Folder 271)
    - Sechler, Susan - 1996, 1993-1995 (Box 20, Folder 272)
    - Seward, Allin C., III, 1987-1996 (Box 20, Folder 273)
    - Sharp, Daniel A., 1979-1987 (Box 20, Folder 274)
    - Sharp, Daniel A., 1988-1994 (Box 20, Folder 275)
    - Shear, David, 1987-2000 (Box 20, Folder 276)
    - Sheffield, Jill W., 1988-1995 (Box 20, Folder 277)
    - Sheinkman, Jacob, 1989-1994 (Box 20, Folder 278)
    - Shelton-Colby, Sally, 1987-1993 (Box 20, Folder 279)
    - Shepard, David H., 1969-1991 (Box 20, Folder 280)
    - Simmons, Adele, 1987-1997 (Box 20, Folder 281)
    - Singh, Manmohan, 1993-1999 (Box 20, Folder 282)
    - Siren, Michaela - 1996, 1993-1996 (Box 21, Folder 283)
    - Slawson, Paul S., 1988-1994 (Box 21, Folder 284)
    - Skolnikoff, Eugene B., 1977-1998 (Box 21, Folder 285)
    - Sommers, Davidson, Esq., 1983-1998 (Box 21, Folder 286)
    - Speth, James Gustave, 1990-1999 (Box 21, Folder 287)
    - Steinberg, Elliot G., 1990-1999 (Box 21, Folder 288)
    - Strong, Maurice, 1988-1992 (Box 21, Folder 289)
    - Sutherland, Peter - Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 290)
    - Sutherland, Peter - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 291)
    - Sutherland, Peter - Correspondence, 1998-2000 (Box 21, Folder 292)
    - Sutherland, Peter - Papers/Documents, 1993-2000 (Box 22, Folder 293)
    - Stern, Paula, 1987-1998 (Box 22, Folder 294)
    - Taylor, Humphrey, 1985-1999 (Box 22, Folder 295)
    - Telhami, Shipley - 1996, 1993-1995 (Box 22, Folder 296)
    - Tether, Harry R. - 1995, 1992-1994 (Box 22, Folder 297)
    - Tierney, Paul E., Jr. - 1995, 1991-1998 (Box 22, Folder 298)
    - Timpson, Sarah L. - 1995, 1992-1996 (Box 22, Folder 299)
    - Tinker, Irene, 1988-2000 (Box 22, Folder 300)
    - Tolles, Theodore L., 1988-1996 (Box 22, Folder 301)
    - Tung, Ko-Yung, Esq., 1990-1995 (Box 22, Folder 302)
    - Ul Haq, Dr. Mahbub, 1993-1999 (Box 22, Folder 303)
    - Ungar, Stanford J., 1988-1999 (Box 22, Folder 304)
    - van Vlierdan, Constant M., 1979-1995 (Box 22, Folder 305)
    - Walsh, Michaela, 1988-1995 (Box 23, Folder 306)
    - Walters, Ronald, 1988-1996 (Box 23, Folder 307)
    - Wapenhans, Willi, 1995-1999 (Box 23, Folder 308)
    - Watts, Glenn E., 1987-1990 (Box 23, Folder 309)
    - Weigand, William K., 1990-1998 (Box 23, Folder 310)
    - Wells, Louis T., Jr., 1988-1995 (Box 23, Folder 311)
    - Wharton, Clifton R., 1984-2000 (Box 23, Folder 312)
    - White, William S., 1987-2000 (Box 23, Folder 313)
    - Williams, Yvonne L., 1988-1996 (Box 23, Folder 314)
    - Wilson, Ernest J., III, 1991-1999 (Box 23, Folder 315)
    - Wirthlin, Richard B., 1991-1994 (Box 23, Folder 316)
    - Wolff, Alan W., Esq., 1988-1995 (Box 23, Folder 317)
    - Young, Andrew, 1980-1995 (Box 23, Folder 318)
    - Yudelman, Sally, 1988-1998 (Box 23, Folder 319)
    - Zapanta, Albert, 1990-1998 (Box 23, Folder 320)
    - Zeidenstein, George, 1980-1991 (Box 23, Folder 321)
    - Zoellick, Rovert - 1996, 1994-1999 (Box 24, Folder 322)
    - Zorthian, Barry, 1981-1992 (Box 24, Folder 323)
- Meetings, 1985-2000; 3; 3.42 Cubic Feet 9 letter document boxes
  - ODC Board Telecon, 2000 October 30 (Box 24, Folder 324)
  - ODC Executive Committee Telecon, 2000 September 13 (Box 24, Folder 325)
  - ODC Executive Committee Telecon, 2000 September 27 (Box 24, Folder 326)
  - ODC Executive Committee Telecon, 2000 April 26 (Box 24, Folder 327)
  - ODC Executive Committee Telecon, 2000 October 11 (Box 24, Folder 328)
  - ODC Executive Committee Telecon, 2000 September 19 (Box 24, Folder 329)
  - ODC Executive Committee Telecon, 2000 June 9 (Box 24, Folder 330)
  - Board Meeting, 2000 March 7-8 (Box 24, Folder 331)
  - Board Meeting Transcript, 1998 October 14; Contains digital material. (Box 24, Folder 332)
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
  - Board & Council Membership, 1998 March (Box 24, Folder 333)
  - Executive Committee Meeting - Conference Call, 1998 December 9 (Box 24, Folder 334)
  - Executive Session of the Executive Committee, 1998 January 23 (Box 24, Folder 335)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1999 May 12 (Box 25, Folder 336)
  - Executive Committee, 1999 September 24, December 3 (Box 25, Folder 337)
  - Meeting of the ODC Executive Committee, 1999 September 24 (Box 25, Folder 338)
  - ODC Board & Council Membership, 2000 May (Box 25, Folder 339)
  - Meeting of the ODC Executive Committee, 2000 March 8 (Box 25, Folder 340)
  - Meeting of the ODC Board of Directors, 2000 March 8 (Box 25, Folder 341)
  - Meeting of the ODC Board of Directors, 1999 March 19 (Box 25, Folder 342)
  - Meeting of the ODC Board of Directors, 1999 March 19 (Box 25, Folder 343)
  - ODC Board & Council Membership, 1999 May (Box 25, Folder 344)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1999 February 16 (Box 26, Folder 345)
  - Executive Committee Meeting - Misc, 1999 September 24 (Box 26, Folder 346)
  - Executive Committee Executive Session, 1999 February 16 (Box 26, Folder 347)
  - Meeting of the ODC Board of Directors, 1998 October 14 (Box 26, Folder 348)
  - Appendices, 1998 October 14 (Box 26, Folder 349)
  - ODC Meeting of the Board of Directors, 1998 March 20 (Box 26, Folder 350)
  - Executive Committee, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 351)
  - ODC Executive Committee Meeting, 1998 March 19 (Box 26, Folder 352)
  - Meeting of the ODC Executive Committee, 1998 September 25 (Box 26, Folder 353)
  - ODC Executive Committee Meeting, 1998 July 17 (Box 26, Folder 354)
  - Board Meeting Transcript, 1998 March 20 (Box 26, Folder 355)
  - Board Meeting Attendance Responces, 1998 March 20 (Box 26, Folder 356)
  - Board Meeting - Misc., 1998 March 20 (Box 26, Folder 357)
  - Meeting of the Board of Directors, 1997 October 15 (Box 27, Folder 358)
  - Board Meeting Transcript, 1997 October 15 (Box 27, Folder 359)
  - ODC Executive Committee Meeting, 1997 September 17 (Box 27, Folder 360)